mediapiston.com 2012-08-26

# MediaPiston | Privacy Policy

#### Last updated: 1-12-2012

Protecting your privacy is important to us. This document describes the privacy policy of MediaPiston, a service and subsidiary of oDesk Corporation, a California corporation with its principal place of business at 901 Marshall Street, Redwood City, California U.S.A. 

This Privacy Policy discusses how MediaPiston gathers, uses, and transmits the personal information you might provide while using MediaPiston and its related services ("MediaPiston"). This policy only applies to information that you provide while using the MediaPiston service and not information collected outside of our services. 

1\. Your Consent 

In using MediaPiston, you consent to MediaPiston's collection, storage and use of any personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, you may choose to not use the MediaPiston service. 

2\. Automatically Collected Information 

Non-Personal Info - the Website automatically collects certain non-personal information such as the date and time you access the Website, your IP address, the URL you accessed and the referring URL, the operating system you are using and any content you post to the Website. This information is stored and may be disclosed to others and permanently archived for future use. 

Cookies - as is commonplace on the internet, we use cookies (alphanumeric identifiers) to associate your browser and computer with your use of the Website. The information you provide while using MediaPiston may be stored in these cookies or may be stored on our servers, depending on the information. You may take steps to block or remove cookies at anytime but the site may not function properly if you do. 

Pixel tags - from time to time, we may place special tracking images in emails or other information that we send you to. These are used so that we determine if a particular piece of email or other communication has been delivered and opened successfully by you. 

3rd Party Web Component - from time to time, we may use 3rd party web components such as display advertising, maps or rich text editors. In such cases, these 3rd parties may collect information subject to the privacy policy of that 3rd party, not MediaPiston's Privacy Policy. 

3\. How MediaPiston Uses the Information 

Operations - we use the information collected to respond to your requests, to operate the site and MediaPiston services, and to maintain operations of the Website. 

Marketing - If you contribute to the site as a writer or editor on our virtual content creation staff, we may use your personal or biographical information to promote and market the contributions you send us as well as to promote and market the MediaPiston service. 

Contact - We use the information you provide in order to contact you when necessary about your order or work status, site functionality and other purposes. 

Retention - We store the information for as long as we believe it useful or necessary, but do not undergo any obligation to retain information indefinitely. We may dispose of information without prior notice. 

4\. Sharing of Information 

3rd Party Services - we may share the information we collect with 3rd party advertisers, service providers and other persons with whom we conduct business. 

Change in Control - in the event that we sell our business or engage in mergers, restructurings, changes of control or other such transaction. In such events any information we collect will be subject to a transfer. In the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, customer and user information may be transferred to a bankruptcy trustee or debtor in possession and then to a subsequent purchaser. 

Corporate Affiliates - We may share the information we collect with business entities that we control or are under common control, such as in joint ventures. Any use of your information is subject to the terms of this policy. 

Compliance - We may share your information in order to comply with applicable laws and to respond to legal processes, including subpoenas, search warrants and court orders, and to respond to or otherwise address written complaints of copyright infringement. We may also share the information to protect MediaPiston interests including sharing select information with credit risk or fraud protection companies. 

5\. Policy Changes - to accommodate changes in our business, we may change or amend this Policy at any time at MediaPiston's sole discretion and without any prior notice to you. 

6\. Your comments - if you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please contact by email at info@mediapiston.com or write us at: 

MediaPiston c/o oDesk Corporation 

901 Marshall Street 

Redwood City, CA 94063
